Guide to the Brooklyn playbills and programs collection BCMS.0041
Brooklyn Collection
- Columbia Theatre
  - Around The World In 80 Days, December 30, 1901 (Box 1)
    A Spectacular Drama In Seven Acts and Twelve Tableaux, By arrangement with Mr. W.J. Fleming, with Frank E. Camp, Asa Willard, John Daly Murphy, E.L. Snader, Fred Hawley, et al. Staged and directed under the supervision of Mr. Wm. Lytell.
  - A Celebrated Case, April 21, 1902 (Box 1)
    In a Prologue and Four Acts. With Frank E. Camp, James A. Bliss, E.L. Snader, John E. Birch, Avon Beyer, Valerie Bergere, et al.
  - King John, March 9, 1903 (Box 1)
    A Tragedy by William Shakespeare, Produced under the personal direction of J. Sidney Macy. Starring R.D. McLean and Odette Tyler, supported By The Columbia Theatre Stock Company. Also with Robert Elliott, Horace Mitchell, J. Sydney Macy, et al.
  - By The Sad Sea Waves, August 31, 1903 (Box 1)
    The Wells-Dunne-Harlan Musical Comedy Company presents "By The Sad Sea Waves." Direction of Mr. John W. Dunne. In the Sparkling Melange of Mirth and Music, with Otis Harlan, Little Chip, David Andrada, et al.
  - The Knickerbocker Girl, October 19, 1903 (Box 1)
    A Musical Comedy in Two Acts. Book by George Totten Smith, Music by Alfred E. Aarons. The Wells-Dunne-Harlan Musical Comedy Company, Direction of John W. Dunne. With Robert Harty, Otis Harlan, Little Chip, W.H. Hatter, et al.
  - The Mocking Bird, October 26 ,1903 (Box 1)
    Mr. Brady Greer presents "The Mocking Bird." Libretto by Sidney Rosenfeld, Music by A. Baldwin Sloane. With Madeline Besley, assisted by Edgar Atchison Ely and Original N.Y. Bijou Theatre Company. Also with Roland Carter, Herbert J. Carter, et al.
  - Paul Revere, November 9, 1903 (Box 1)
    Henry B. Marks presents Mr. Richard Buhler in, Frederick Gibb's Romantic Drama, "Paul Revere." Also with Mr. Howard C. Hickman, Mr. George A. Lemming, Mr. Chas. McDonald, Miss Carrie Lamort, et al.
  - Southern Enchantment, March 21, 1904 (Box 1)
    The Smart Set in a Three Act and Seven Scene Extravaganza. Book by S.B. Casson, Ensemble Music by Leo. Merriman, Musical Numbers and Drills staged by Jack Mason. With Ernest Hogan, John Bailey, J. Ed. Green, et al.
- Commodore
  - The Secret Studio, August 8-14, 1927 (Box 1)
    "The Secret Studio" with Olive Borden, A Corking Good Comedy; "White Pants Willie", A Comedy with Johnny Hines.
  - The Shepherd of the Hills, October 2-8, [1941] (Box 1)
    By Harold Bell Wright, with John Wayne, et al. Plus "There's Magic In Music" with Allan Jones, Susanna Foster, et al. "The Officer And The Lady" with Rochelle Hudson, Bruce Bennett, et al. And "Bachelor Daddy, Baby Sandy" with Donald Woods, et al.
  - Hold Back the Dawn, February 5-11, [1942] (Box 1)
    "Hold Back The Dawn" with Charles Boyer; "Henry Aldrich For President", with Jimmy Lydon; "Flying Cadets" with William Gargan; "Ellery Queen And The Murder Ring" with Ralph Bellamy; "You Belong To Me" with Barbara Stanwyck; and more.
  - Johnny Eager, May 7-13, [1942?] (Box 1)
    A Mervyn LeRoy Production with Rob't Taylor; "Born To Sing" with Virginia Weidler, Directed by Edward Ludwig, Produced by Frederick Stephani; "Sailors On Leave" with William Lundigan; Also "Harvard Here I Come" with "Slapsie" Maxie Rosenbloom.
  - The Invaders, May 14-22, [1942] (Box 1)
    "The Invaders" with Laurence Olivier, Leslie Howard; "Lady For A Night" with Joan Blondell and John Wayne; "The Bugle Sounds" Starring Wallace Beery; "Sealed Lips" with William Gargan.
  - Tin Pan Alley, September 9-14, [1942] (Box 1)
    "Tin Pan Alley"with Alice Faye, Betty Grable; Plus "Swiss Family Robinson" with Thomas Mitchell; "Crossroads" with William Powell and Hedy Lamarr; "Friendly Enemies" with Charles Winninger, Directed By Allan Dwan.
- Crescent Theatre
  - [Photograph of T. A. Forbes, Crescent Stock Company], [1900] (Box 1)
    Photograph of T. A. Forbes, a part of the Crescent Stock Company for the Crescent Theatre.
  - The Battle Of Gettysburg, June 29, 1913 (Box 1)
    The Mutual Film Corporation presents "The Battle Of Gettysburg," A Spectacular American Photoplay in Five Reels. Produced by the New York Motion Picture Corporation.Under The Direction of Thomas H. Ince - Managing Director, Kay-Bee and Broncho Films.
  - Common Clay, November 17, 1919 (Box 1)
    A Drama In Three Acts and an Epilogue, By Cleves Kinkead. The Corse Playton Stock Company, with Mary Richards, Jack Bryce, Ester Small, Bruno Wicks, Belle Mitchell, et al. The Crescent Theatre Orchestra under the direction of Otto W. Liebing.
  - Madame X, December 1, 1919 (Box 1)
    In Three Acts And A Prologue. Adapted from the French of Alexander Bisson by John Raphael. The Corse Payton Stock Campany, with Henriette Browne, Reynolds Evans, Louis Leon Hall, et al. The Crescent Theatre Orchestra directed by Otto W. Liebing.
- Criterion
  - Caprice, November 1, [1880] (Box 1)
    "Caprice" by Howard P. Taylor, Esq. Engagement of America's Distinguished Ingenue Miss Maddern, with William Morris, Mr. T.J. Herndon, Mr. D.G. Longworth, Miss Odette Tyler, Miss Mary Maddern, Miss Addie Baker, et al. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
  - Leah, the Forsaken, March 22, 1895 (Box 1)
    Booth Dramatic Society presenting "Leah, the Forsaken," a play in five acts by Augustin Daly.
  - A Midnight Bell, April 26, 1895 (Box 1)
    Booth Dramatic Society presenting..."A Midnight Bell," by Charles H. Hoyt.
  - A Boy Hero, May 28, [no year] (Box 1)
    Martin Hayden, supported by a Company of First-class Artists, in the Nautical Melo-Drama, "A Boy Hero." Produced with Special Scenery and Mechanical Effects. Under The Management Of Mr. Harry Bernard.
- Cumberland
  - Sunny Side Up, May 23-29, 1930 (Box 1)
    "Sunny Side Up" with Janet Gaynor and Charles Farrell; King Vidor's "Hallelujah!"; "The Marriage Playground" with Mary Brian, Fredric March; Also Ted Lewis in "Is Everybody Happy?" with Ann Pennington.
- Decatur
  - You're Out Of Luck, April 20-26, [1941] (Box 1)
    "You're Out Of Luck" with Frankie Darro; "Lone Star Raiders" with 3 Mesquiteers; "Boobs in Arms" 3 Stooges; Ch. 4 "White Eagle" with Buck Jones; "Flight Command" with Robert Taylor; "White Zombie" with Bela Lugosi; "Comrade X" with Clark Gable; and more.
  - Bowery Boy, June 22-28, [1941] (Box 1)
    "Bowery Boy" with Dennis O'Keefe; "The Fargo Kid" with Tim Holt Sund; "Rage in Heaven" with Robert Montgomery; "Model Wife" with Joan Blondell; "Shark Woman" and "Design For Murder"; "Sons Of The Legion" with Lynne Overman; and more.
  - Law of the Jungle, April 19-25, [1944] (Box 1)
    "Law of the Jungle" with Arline Judge; "West of Tombstone" with Charles Starrett; "Three Girls About Town" with Joan Blondell; "The Richest Man In Town" with Frank Craven; "3 Sons O'Guns" with Wayne Morris; "The Nurse's Secret" with Lee Patrick; and more.
- DeKalb
  - The High Cost of Loving, December 28, 1914 (Box 1)
    A.H. Woods presents Lew Fields in "The High Cost Of Loving," a Novel Repast in Three Courses by Frank Mandel, adapted from the German. Also with Alice Fischer, Grace Meinken, George Hassell, Charlotte Ives, et al.
  - Peg O' My Heart, February 15, 1913 (Box 1)
    Oliver Morosco presents "Peg O'My Heart," a Comedy in Three Acts, by J. Hartley Manners. Staged by T. Daniel Frawley, General Stage Director of the Morosco Productions. With Lisle Leigh, Peter Bassett, Alma Tell, Hassard Short, Lewis Broughton, et al.
- Eden
  - The Farmer's Daughter, November 3-9, [no year] (Box 1)
    "The Farmer's Daughter" with Marjorie Beebe, Warren Burke, also 2-Act Comedy - "Elephant's Elbows"; "Fazil" with Charles Farrell and Greta Nissen. In conjunction with this production, Mr. J. Howe will appear in person to sing the theme song.
- Embassy
  - Meet Me After The Show, September 26-October 17, [no year] (Box 1)
    "Meet Me After The Show" with Betty Grable; "Alice In Wonderland" by Walt Disney; "That's My Boy" with Dean Martin and Jerry Lewis, by Hal Wallis; "Jim Thorpe - All American" with Burt Lancaster, Charles Bickford.
- Empire
  - Michael Shayne, Private Detective, February 16-24, [1941] (Box 1)
    "Michael Shayne, Private Detective" with Lloyd Nolan; "Little Men" with Kay Francis; "Bitter Sweet" by Noel Coward, with Jeanette Mac Donald; "Angels Over Broadway" with Douglas Fairbanks, Jr.; "Chad Hanna" with Henry Fonda; and more.
  - The Broadway Burlesquers, January 29, [no year] (Box 1)
    "The Broadway Burlesquers": Olio; Carlin Sisters; The Ginger Girls, Mr. Lew Wells, In Musical Comedy; Emma Carus, The Baritone; Gilbert and Goldie, Character Comedians; McAvoy and May, in a "Crazy Conglomeration"; and others.
- Farragut
  - A Woman Rebels, November, 1936 (Box 1)
    "A Woman Rebels" with Katharine Hepburn as Pamela and Herbert Marshall, also with Elizabeth Allan, Donald Crisp, Doris Dudley, Lucille Watson, et al.
- Flatbush Theatre (Brandt's)
  - Michael And Mary, April 20, 1931 (Box 1)
    "Michael And Mary," a Comedy by A.A. Milne, staged by Mr. Charles Hopkins, designed by Thomas Farrar. With Jos. M. Gaites, Madge Kennedy, George Spelvin, Terence Heill, Virginia Wallace, et al.
  - Strike Me Pink, March 28, 1936 (Box 1)
    "Strike Me Pink" with Eddie Cantor, Ethel Merman; "Guard That Girl" with Robert Allan; "Three Kids And A Queen" with May Robson; "Mary Burns, Fugitive" with Sylvia Sidney; "Dangerous" with Bette Davis; "Broadway Hostess" with Wini Shaw.
  - The Story Of Louis Pasteur, April 11, 1936 (Box 1)
    "The Story Of Louis Pasteur" with Paul Muni; "Ceiling Zero" with James Cagney; "King of Burlesque" with Warner Baxter; "Charlie Chan's Secret" with Warner Oland; "Peter Ibbetson" with Gary Cooper; "Paddy O'Day" with Jane Withers.
  - Accent On Youth, July 15, 1941 (Box 1)
    "Accent On Youth," Samson Raphaelson's Comedy. With Sylvia Sidney, Luther Adler, Clyde M. Waddell, Valerie Valaire, Kevin McCarthy, et al. Staged by the Author.
  - Tobacco Road, August 5, 1941 (Box 1)
    "Tobacco Road" a play in Three Acts by Jack Kirkland. Based on the novel by Erskine Caldwell. Directed by Anthony Brown, Settings by Robert Reddington Sharpe. With John Barton, Robert Rose, Sara Perry, Merryl Boyden, et al.
  - Theatre, May 12, 1942 (Box 1)
    "Theatre" by Guy Bolton and Somerset Maugham. A Comedy with Elissa Landi, Sanford Bickart, Olive Reeves-Smith, Bram Nossen, et al. Staged by Robert Burton, Settings by Donald Oenslager.
  - Watch on the Rhine, June 30, 1942 (Box 1)
    "Watch on the Rhine," a drama by Lillian Hellman. Settings by Jo Mielziner. With Eda Heinemann, Zamah Cunningham, Charles Benjamin, Coburn Goodwin, Hattie Richardson, Alexander Clark, Zelya Talma, et al. Song composed by Paul Bowles.
  - Porgy and Bess, May 9, 1944 (Box 1)
    "Porgy and Bess" by George Gershwin and DuBose Heyward. With Etta Moten, William Franklin and The Eva Jessye Choir conducted by Alexander Smallens. Music by G. Gershwin, Book by DuBose Heyward, Lyrics by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin.
  - Early To Bed, June 6, 1944 (Box 1)
    Richard Kollmar's Musical Comedy, "Early To Bed." Book & Lyrics by George Marion, Jr. Music by Thomas "Fats" Waller. Score orchestrated by Don Walker. With Joseph Macaulay, Bob Howard, Ruth Webb, Ann Parker, et al.
  - Tomorrow The World, September 4, 1944 (Box 1)
    "Tomorrow The World" by James Gow and Arnaud d'Usseau. Setting Designed by Raymond Sovey. With Conrad Nagel, Joan Shepard, Violet Dunn, Lilia Rock, Johanna Douglas, Johnnie Venn, Richard Taber, et al.
  - Arsenic and Old Lace, September 19, 1944 (Box 1)
    "Arsenic and Old Lace," a Comedy by Joseph Kesselring. With Helen Twelvetrees, Catherine Proctor, Clyde Veaux, Winifred St. Claire, Freeman Hammond, Gordon G. Peters, Loy Nilson, et al. Setting by Raymond Sovey.
  - Angel Street, May 15, 1945 (Box 1)
    Shepard Traube presents "Angel Street" by Patrick Hamilton. Staged by Mr. Traube, Setting and Costumes designed by Lemuel Ayers. With Viola Keats, Brent Sargent, Jetti Preminger, Daisy Belmore, and Cecil Humphreys.
  - The Heiress, July 5, 1949 (Box 1)
    "The Heiress" by Ruth and Augustus Goetz. Suggested by Henry James' novel "Washington Square." With Miriam Hopkins, Ralph Forbes, Winifred St. Claire, Kathleen Comegys, Norma Winslow, et al. Directed by Stanley Gould, Settings by Louis Kennel.
  - High Button Shoes, August 9, 1949 (Box 1)
    "High Button Shoes," A Musical Comedy. Music and Lyrics by Jule Styne and Sammy Cahn, Book by Stephen Longstreet, Settings by Oliver Smith, Costumes by Miles White, Dances conceived by Jerome Robbins. With Joey Faye, Dan Dayton, Louis Ampolo, et al.
  - The Member of the Wedding, May 5, 1952 (Box 1)
    Robert Whitehead, Oliver Rea and Stanley Martineau present "The Member Of The Wedding" by Carson McCullers. With Ethel Waters, Betty Lou Holland, James Holden, et al. Directed by Harold Clurman. Setting, Costumes and Lighting by Lester Polakov.
- Flatbush Theatre (Werba's)
  - Those We Love, February 10, 1930 (Box 1)
    Philip Dunning presents "Those We Love," a play in Three Acts. By George Abbott and S. K. Lauren. With Madeline King, Natalie Potter, John Stokes, Helen Flint, George Brent, Percy Kilbride, et al. Staged by George Abbott.
  - Brothers, March 17, 1930 (Box 1)
    John Henry Mears presents"Brothers" by Herbert Ashton, Jr. Staged by Arthur Hurley, Art Direction by Yellenti. With Bert Lytell, Ben MacQuarrie, William Ingersoll, Frank Sylvester, James Seeley, Clara Palmer, et al.
- Folly Theatre
  - Sis Hopkins, March 21, 1904 (Box 1)
    J.R. Stirling presents (5th Season) the Artistic Comedienne Rose Melville in "Sis Hopkins." Also with Florence Webster, Blanche Carlisle, Malvina Arment, James McDuff, Frank C. Hartwell et al.
  - By Right of Sword, March 28, 1904 (Box 1)
    Ralph Stuart Presents "By Right of Sword" a Romantic Comedy In Four Acts, by Mrs. Elizabeth Doremus, Leonidas Westervelt, in Collaboration with A.W. Marchmont. With Ralph Stuart, J.R. Armstrong, Jacques Caldwell et al.
  - Out of the Fold, May 9, 1904 (Box 1)
    "Out Of The Fold" by Langdon McCormick. Direction, Henry Weil. With Dave Murray, Joseph Manning, A.L. McCormick, George Fox, John Brinsley, Miss Frank Lawrence, Louise Whitehouse et al.
  - Mr. Blarney from Ireland, January 29, 1906 (Box 1)
    Fiske O'Hara in "Mr. Blarney from Ireland" by Chas. Blaney. Staged by Jas. R. Garey, General Stage Director. Also with J.P. Sullivan, Edwin A. Sparks, W.F. Walcott, John Martin, George Cooper et al.
- Fulton Theatre
  - Superb Vaudeville, [c. 1908-1909] (Box 1)
    William E. Slafer and His Orchestra; Deas and Deas; George C. Davis; Lowe-Lewin Martel, xylophone virtuosi; May Tully and Company in "Stop, Look and Listen," Matthew White, Jr.'s one-act play; Scottish comedians; Morriscope; and more. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
- Gayety Theatre
  - The Governors, March 13, 1899 (Box 1)
    E. D. Stair presents Ward and Vokes in Their Variety Farce, "The Governors." With Happy Ward, Harry Vokes, Sam Collins, Chas. W. Young, John Keefe, Hal S. Stephens et al.
  - On Board the City Club, November 17, 1902 (Box 1)
    Rush & Fulton's City Club Burlesquers performing "On Board the City Club." Also featuring, Olio; Rose Carlin; Hawthorne & Burt; Mlle. Junette Perie; Three Lane Sisters; Reid & Gilbert; Mons. And Mlle. Paxton's Living Art Panorama; Greve & Greene.
  - Fun in the Subway, January 11, 1909 (Box 1)
    Rialto Rounders, The Girlie Show in "Fun In The Subway," A Racy Concoction of Music, Women and Frivolity. Written and Staged by Sam S. Howe, with Sam Howe, Eddie Lovett, Al. Davis, Bert Harvey, Joe Milton, Juan Villisant et. al.
  - Victory Belles, February 6, 1922 (Box 1)
    "Victory Belles" with Elinor Mack, Emma Wilson, Lil Harrison, Vie Kelly, Bobby Wilson et al.
  - The Big Review, April 3, 1922 (Box 1)
    "The Big Review" in Two Acts and Five Scenes, with Nancy Martin, Joe Freels, Lettie Boles, Sam Boles, Sam Raynor et al.
- Gilbert Dramatic Association
  - Uncle Dick's Darling, January 17, 1887 (Box 1)
    "Uncle Dick's Darling" by Henry J. Byron, with Chas. T. Catlin, Geo. W. Cogan, John F. Dyer et al. Followed by "Woodcock's Little Game" by J.M. Morton, with M. Lindeman, Hattie F. Nefflen et al. John Billings, Director. Wm. B.Vernam, Stage Manager.
  - The Jilt [2 copies], November 12, 1888 (Box 1)
    "The Jilt" a comedy in Five Acts by Dion Boucicault. With Wm. B. Vernam, John Billings, Jas. Jordan Darling, John W. Noble et al. Director, John Billings. Stage Manager, E. W. Jacobson. Musical Director, E. J. McCormick.
  - How She Loves Him [2 copies], April 10, 1889 (Box 1)
    "How She Loves Him" a comedy, in Six Acts, by Dion Boucicault. With Harry J. Stokum, James J. Darling, Adam Dove, John W. Noble et al. Director, John Billings. Stage Manager, E. W. Jacobson. Musical Director, E. J. McCormick.
  - The Great Pink Pearl [2 copies], February 10, 1890 (Box 1)
    "The Great Pink Pearl" a Comedy in Three Acts, by permission of Daniel Frohman, Esq. With Jas. Jordan Darling, John W. Noble, Harrie J. Stokum et al. Director, Jas. Jordan Darling. Stage Manager, Geo. W. Cogan. Musical Director, E. J. McCormick.
- Globe
  - The Last Train From Madrid, September 12-18, [1937] (Box 1)
    "The Last Train From Madrid"with Dorothy Lamour; "League Of Frightened Men" with Walter Connolly; Chapter 7 of "Painted Stallion"; "Texas Ranger" with Fred MacMurray; "Exclusive Story" with Franchot Tone; "Blue Velvet Music" Musical; and more. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
- Gotham
  - Jim, The Penman [3 copies], February 1, 1909 (Box 1)
    The Gotham Stock Company presents "Jim, The Penman," The Greatest of A.M. Palmer's Successes, with Emma Bell, Miss Bijou Washburn, Miss Josephine Fox, Madame Neuville et al.
- Grand Opera House
  - The Old Homestead, October 11, 1886 (Box 1)
    Denman Thompson will present his New Play, "The Old Homestead," by Denman Thompson and Geo. W. Ryer. A Continuation of "Joshua Whitcomb." With Mr. George A. Beane, Mr. Walter Gale, Mr. J.L. Morgan et al.
  - The Idea, February 20, 1893 (Box 1)
    Hallen and Hart in Their New Comic Play. "The Idea," by Herbert Hall Winslow and Joseph Hart. With Miss Fanny Bloodgood, Miss Mollie Fuller, Miss Alice Fuller, Miss Alice Carle, Frederick Hallen et al.
  - The Governors, December 27, 1897 (Box 1)
    Ward and Vokes In "The Governors," A Musical Comedy, In Three Acts, by Fred S. Gibbs. Tour directed by E.D. Stair. With Happy Ward, Harry Vokes, Johnny Page, Gus. C. Weinberg, Margaret Daly Vokes, Vila Sayne et al.
  - A Hot Old Time, February 21, 1898 (Box 1)
    The Rays in "A Hot Old Time," the Three-Act Musical Farce, By and under the Management of Edgar Selden. With Mr. Johnny Ray, John C. Leach, Frank Lalor, Madeline Marshall, Kitty Nelson et al.
  - Chimes of Normandy, May 2, 1898 (Box 1)
    The Jaxon Opera Company, under the personal supervision of Mr. J.J. Jaxon, in "Chimes of Normandy," An Opera In Three Acts, by Planquette. With Mr. Winfred Goff, Mr. Payne Carke, Mr. Frank Deshon et al.
  - Lucia di Lammermoor, May 23, 1898 (Box 1)
    The Jaxon Opera Company, under the personal supervision of Mr. J.J. Jaxon, in "Lucia Di Lammermoor," Grand Opera In Four Acts, by Donizetti. With Miro Delamotta,Winfred Goff et al. Also, "The Bohemian Girl" An Opera, In Three Acts, by Balfe.
  - Great American Minstrels, January 23, 1899 (Box 1)
    Primrose & Dockstader's Great American Minstrels. Management of J.H. Decker. With Primrose & Dockstader's Sextette, Jimmy Wall, Manuel Romain, Quaker City Quartette et al.
  - A Wise Guy, October 2, 1899 (Box 1)
    Hayes and Lytton in "A Wise Guy." Also with Mr. Edmond Hayes, Joe Welch, Ray L. Royce, Chas. Moreland, Louise Montrose, Minnie May Thompson, Emily Lytton et al.
  - The Rising Generation, December 18, 1899 (Box 1)
    William Barry, in the latest revision of "The Rising Generation," by William Gill. Also with James H. Manning, Alban W. Purcell, Robert Barry, Willie Weston, William Robbins, Lily Fitzgerald, Addie Doyle and Margaret Hatch.
  - The Girl From Maxim's, September 30, 1901 (Box 1)
    "The Girl From Maxim's," A Farce, In Three Acts, by George Feydeau, Author of "The Gay Parisians." Direction of Julius Cahn, with Mr. W.H. Turner, Joseph Allen, Harry Dull, John H. Armstrong, Dwight Smith, Rowland Hill et al.
  - The Governor's Son, October 7, 1901 (Box 1)
    L.C. Behman presents The Four Cohans in "The Governor's Son." Book and Music by George M. Cohan. With Jerry J. Cohan, Geo. M. Cohan, Wm. Keough, Will H. Sloan, James H. Manning, Ethel Levey, Josephine Kirkwood et al.
  - The Awakening of Mr. Pipp, April 25, 1904 (Box 1)
    Charley Grapewin in "The Awakening of Mr. Pipp," A Farce with Melodic and Terpsichorean Incidentals for Entertaining Purposes, In Three Acts and Five Scenes, By George Totten Smith and Charley Grapewin. Also with, Nellie Beaumont, Luke Sylvester et al.
  - Tom, Dick and Harry, October 23, 1905 (Box 1)
    A.H. Woods presents Bickel, Watson and Worthe in "Tom, Dick And Harry." Direction of A.H. Woods, Book and Lyrics by Harry Williams and Aaron Hoffman, Music by Egbert Van Alstyne, Staged by Miss Gertrude Huffman. With Harry Bond, Samuel Brobst et al.
  - Robin Hood, December 23, 1907 (Box 1)
    Milton and Sargent Aborn present the Aborn Opera Company, in a Revival of the Bostonians' Famous Success, "Robin Hood." Music by Reginald DeKoven, Book by Harry B. Smith. With Forrest Huff, Phil Branson, Harry Luckstone et al.
  - Il Trovatore, January 6, 1908 (Box 1)
    Milton and Sargent Aborn present the Aborn Opera Company, in Guiseppe Verdi's, "Il Trovatore." In English, with Estelle Wentworth, Alice Craft Benson, Miriam Norris, Amelia Fields, Joseph Fredericks, Henry M. Barron, Frederic Chapman et al.
  - Gertrude Hoffmann And The Mimic World, October 26, 1908 (Box 1)
    "Gertrude Hoffmann And The Mimic World," A New Musical Review, In Two Acts and Seven Scenes. Book by Edgar Smith, Lyrics by Ed. Madden and Addison Burkhardt, Music by Ben M. Jerome and Seymour Furth. With Walter Lawrence, Chas. Meyers et al.
  - La Tosca, November 13, [no year] (Box 1)
    Blanche Walsh and Melbourne MacDowell, (Under the direction of Ben. Stern), in Sardou's Great Play, "La Tosca." Also with Arthur Elliot, James E. Nelson et al. Also Sardou's Historical Drama "Gismonda" and Sardou's "Fedora."
- Greenpoint
  - Four Clovelly Girls, September 25, 1911 (Box 1)
    Performances: E. A. Thornell's Greenpoint Orchestra; Four Clovelly Girls; Harriet Burt; Fred St. Onge Troupe; Chadwick Trio; Mrs. Gene Hughes and Company; Alexander and Scott; Trovato; Victor Moore and Co.; The Vitagraph.
- Grove
  - The Women, January 7-10, [1940] (Box 1)
    "The Women" with Joan Crawford; "The Man They Could Not Hang" with Boris Karloff; "Find The Witness" with Charles Quigley; "She Married Her Boss" with Claudette Colbert; "Thunder Afloat" with Wallace Beery; "Disputed Passage" with Dorothy Lamour.
  - Kid Galahad, August 15-21, [1937] (Box 1)
    "Kid Galahad" with Bette Davis; "Oh Doctor" with Edward Everett Horton; "Turn Off The Moon" with Charlie Ruggles; "Draegerman Courage" with Jean Muir; "Woman Chases Man" with Miriam Hopkins; "Silent Barriers" with Richard Arlen; and more. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
  - The Toast Of New York, October 3-9, [1937] (Box 1)
    "The Toast Of New York" with Cary Grant; "Motor Madness" with Rosalind Keith; "Traveling Saleslady" with Joan Blondell; "Mystery of the Wax Museum" with Fay Wray; "Silver Dollar" with Edward G. Robinson; "Employes' Entrance" with Loretta Young; & more. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
- Halsey
  - When Knighthood Was in Flower, February 5, 1923 (Box 1)
    Marion Davies in the Paramount Picture, "When Knighthood Was in Flower." Katherine MacDonald in "The Woman Conquers." Also, Eileen Percy in The Flirt." With Usual Big Vaudeville.
- Hansa Theatre